<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Researjour</string>

    <string name="terms">Welcome to Researjour!</string>
    <string name="first_para">These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of Researjour\'s Website, located at www.researjour.com.</string>
    <string name="second_para">By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Researjour if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.</string>
    <string name="third_para">The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: "Client", "You" and "Your" refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions. "The Company", "Ourselves", "We", "Our" and "Us", refers to our Company. "Party", "Parties", or "Us", refers to both the Client and ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of Netherlands. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.</string>
    <string name="fourth_para">Cookies</string>
    <string name="fifth_para">We employ the use of cookies. By accessing Researjour, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the Researjour\'s Privacy Policy.

Most interactive websites use cookies to let us retrieve the user’s details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easie r for people visiting our website. Some of our affiliate/advertising partners may also use cookies.</string>
    <string name="sixth_para">License</string>
    <string name="seventh_para">Unless otherwise stated, Researjour and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on Researjour. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from Researjour for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="eight_para">You must not:

Republish material from Researjour
Sell, rent or sub-license material from Researjour
Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from Researjour
Redistribute content from Researjour
This Agreement shall begin on the date here of.</string>
    <string name="app_logo">app_logo</string>
    <string name="last_name">last name</string>
    <string name="first_name">first name</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="existing_user">Existing User?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="or_register_with">or Register with</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="agree_to">Agree to</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">confirm password</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="terms_amp_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>


    <string name="categoryDesc">You can only choose one category at a time based on your research field</string>
    <string name="subjectDesc">You can only choose multiple subject based on your research field</string>

    //gender spinner items
    <string-array name="gender_spinnerItems">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    //role spinner items
    <string-array name="role_spinnerItems">
        <item>Undergraduate Student</item>
        <item>Master Student</item>
        <item>PhD Student</item>
        <item>Professor/Lecturer</item>
        <item>Commercial Scientist</item>
        <item>Researcher</item>
        <item>Medical Professional/Doctor</item>
        <item>Librarian</item>
        <item>Laboratory Director/Faculty</item>
        <item>Senior Scientist</item>
        <item>Research Director</item>
        <item>Just interested</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    //category items
    <string-array name="category_items">
        <item>Medical &amp; Health Science</item>
        <item>Life Sciences &amp; Biology</item>
        <item>Material Science</item>
        <item>Computer Science</item>
        <item>Social Science</item>
        <item>Geography</item>
        <item>Physics &amp; Mathematics</item>
        <item>Business Management</item>
        <item>Arts &amp; Humanities</item>
        <item>Economics &amp; Finance</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout Successfully</string>
    <string name="our_mission_desc">Researjour’s mission is to become the world’s leading discovery platform for scientists and researchers. We make it easy to stay up to date, so they can concentrate on moving their research forward.</string>
    <string name="our_story_desc">Founded in 2020, we created Researcher to help academics stay afloat in a sea of literature. Keeping up to date with all new papers is a crucial part of any researcher\'s day to day life, but it\'s often difficult to find the time or energy. That\'s where we realised we could help.</string>
    <string name="working_desc">Our team is passionate about helping scientists make their big breakthroughs faster. We\'re growing rapidly, so if you\'re interested in joining our small, dynamic team please get in touch.</string>

</resources>
